Suyeong Park

suyeong.park0@gmail.com | github.com/euphoria0-0

Research Interest

My research interests are mainly on making more **trustworthy AI** tech using collaborations of information in data and knowledge from human beings. I believe 'understanding an intrinsic attributes of things using our knowledge' is crucial for deploying ML models for better human-being life in a real-world. Thus, I'm interested in identifying **Causality** of things from our data for explainable AI while overcoming the limitations of typical ML.

EDUCATION

Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

Ulsan, Korea

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

GPA: 4.15/4.3

Advisor: Prof. Kwang In Kim and Prof. Namhoon Lee

Relevant Coursework: Causal Learning & Explainable AI, Reinforcement Learning, Advanced Machine Learning

Topics, Computer Vision, Principles of Deep Learning

University of Seoul

Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Data Science

Mar. 2015 - Feb. 2020

GPA: 3.7/4.5

Relevant Coursework: Bayesian Statistics, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Time Series Analysis, Multivariate Statistics, Statistical Computing, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics

EXPERIENCE

Visiting Researcher

Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022

CausalML Lab, Purdue University

• Research Project: Bayesian Causal Discovery

Research Assistant

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

Machine Learning and Vision Lab, UNIST

Ulsan, Korea

West Lafayette, US

• Research Projects: active learning, transfer learning, federated learning, image attribute estimation

Intern, Data Analyst and Engineer

Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020

Seoul Big Data Campus

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city

Intern, Data Analyst Assistant

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

FSC (Financial Services Commission)

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Data analysis with financial public data

Publication

S. Park, Y. Ahn, K. Kim. Blind (keyword: Deep Active Learning, Bayesian) [Preprint]

In Submission, 2022

S. Park, Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning [Link] Master's Thesis, 2022

PROJECTS

Visual Common Se	once Through Solf supervis	sed Learning for Restoration of
		sed Learning for Restoration of
Invisible Parts in	ı İmage	

April. 2021 – Aug. 2022

Causal Learning with Artificial Intelligence for genome dataset Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city Mar. 2021 – Dec. 2021 Apr. 2020 – Jun. 2020

Data analysis with financial public data

Jan. 2020 – Feb. 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, R, SQL (MySQL)

Tools: PyTorch, TensorFlow, Git, Docker, PyCharm, VSCode

Others: QGIS, Tableau, SAS

Last Updated: November 15, 2022